ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 1 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 10)
  Includes: Rockettes strike against Radio City Music Hall, New York City; strikers with placards; strikers waving from the police wagon; strikers with placards, Bethlehem PA, 4/19/56; placards for strike against Judy Bond; strikers against Dumont Sportswear; police dragging away a black woman striker; strikers against American Lady Corset Co. march in a corset, Jan. 1941, Detroit, MI; sit in at a department store; strikers with placards against Amboy Knitwear; Union members handing out leaflets against Sears; strikers with placards against Neco Contracting Corp.; Antonini, Hochman, and others on platform with a banner advertising a mass demonstration; Local 62 members strike Spartan Undies, Inc.; strikers against Cable Raincoat Co. in South Boston, Mass., 1955; strikers against Desire Fashions; police take woman away from a sit in at a department store; Antonini at Dress Picket Committee Meeting, 2/17/58; man painting strike placards; strike against Reverie; strikers against Mittelman; strikers against Kulpmont; Local 345 members strike against Tower City Dress, Utica NY, March 1958; strike against Billsway, New Haven, Conn.; workers strike against Cosmopolitan, Boston, Mass., 1955; strike against Henderson Coat Co.; strike against Neptune Garment Company, Boston, Mass.; Workers on strike against Hartsville; workers on strike against Boston Maid; workers protesting the lockout of Local 122 members at Levi Brothers, Georgia, 1960; David Dubinsky - speech; Local 162 members strike against Sterling Neckwear; worker with placard striking Binstrom, Inc.; TWU workers on strike with placards; policeman with four ILGWU picketers, New York City, 1/16/55; David Dubinsky - speech; strikers at Revere Knitting Mill; entrance to Local 102's strike headquarters; strike, April 1960; strike leaders of a Minneapolis ILGWU strike, April 1960; two black women, one with bandage on her eye, and one with a bandage around her arm, from 1941 strike against New York Handkerchief Co., Chicago; Alabama ILGWU members with placards for their locals, Locals 457, 378, 555, 408 represented; striker rides a horse, Homer, New York, 9/1/78; strikers against Malrose Garment Co.; strikers against Klein & Levine Coat Co.; ILGWU organizer distributes minimum wage leaflets to employees of a non-union shop in Atlanta; striker against David Kass Coat Co.; woman punches the owner of Mazzuto's Garment Factory, Newark NJ, Oct. 1935; workers hold up leaflets for General Strike, 1958; picketers with placards against Kellwood products; a severely beaten woman with bandages on her hand, head, and eyes, and blood on her shirt; striking woman wearing only her placard, Aug. 15, 1978; Local 408 members from Tennessee picket in Cleveland; Local 91 members strike against Baby Togs; man with placards protesting several different companies; Local 148-162 members strike against Sears Fashion District Center; strikers against Elaine Coat Co., Lodi New Jersey; strikers against River Park Mfg. Co. Paterson, New Jersey
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 2 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 3 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 4 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 5 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 6 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 7 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 8 of 8] (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 1 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 1)
  Includes: Strikers wearing only corsets strike against American Lady Corset Co., Jan. 1941, Detroit MI; employees strike at Brownhill Kramer Full Fashioned Hosiery Mill, Philadelphia, 1/12/37; Harvard University students join a picket line against Vanta Co., 2/1/46; Women striking Nordeen Co. huddle around a fire; Antonini and David Dubinsky lead the strike of Local 457 against Kayser - Roth, 1959; employees of Carolina Industrial Manufacturing Corp. strike, 3/1/55; Local 155 members strike Devon Knitwear; Hochman, Zimmerman, and Antonini lead an ILGWU mass demonstration; Local 187 members strike Mound Carothers Casket Co.; Local 167 members strike Mayehoff, 1958; Jacobs Bros. employees strike; Local 145 members strike, 1958; Padilla Sportswear workers strike; workers strike against Digby Manufacturing Co., 1958; woman from Local 151 with strike placards, 1958; Jerry Gilden workers strike, 2/25/58; workers strike Mountain Top Co., Hendersonville, North Carolina, 4/28/58; members of Local 415, Miami Florida; workers strike against Franklin - Simon; women with placards for strike against Serbin Inc., Fayetteville, Tenn.; Local 408 members hand out leaflets; policeman talks to Ann Dress Co. strikers, Saugerties New York, 3/17/58; Serbin employees picket on the Alabama - Tennessee state line; workers of River Park Manufacturing Co. strike; Belle Manufacturing Co. workers strike; Queen City Dress Co. workers strike, 3/5/58; three ILGWU men on strike, March 5, 1958; Friedman - Blau - Farber workers on strike; Local 142 workers strike against Kaplan Bros.; police break up strike of W.P.A. artists, 12/1/36; Iris workers on strike; workers of Plymouth Co. on strike, 1955; workers picket Glamour Garment; Serbin workers display placards on their boat; Hartsville Workers on strike; Boston garment workers being arrested, 2/20/30; Revelation Bra Co. workers on strike; the ILGWU convention, Atlantic City, May 1937; women strike Walterboro Mfg. Co.; the end of a sit down strike at Kelsey Hayes, Detroit Michigan, 12/24/36; picketers with placards against Kay Dunhill Dresses; workers strike Topps Coat Co., 8/15/52; worker of Robert Leonard on strike; women strike Padula Sportswear; David Dubinsky speech; women of Local 399 distributing leaflets outside department store, Evansville, Ind., 6/31/59; strikers in Freydberg N. Carolina, July 1954; Milham Products workers on strike; Local 91 members picket Gort Girl; workers strike Kayser - Roth, 1959; David Dubinsky helps the Kayser - Roth picketing; Hymar employees on strike; workers of Mittelman - Bernstein picketing in New York City; Emkay strikers take a break, 8/22/53, W. Wyoming, Pennsylvania; Plasco Co. workers strike; workers strike Hazen Bros.; police arrest woman, 2/26/59; Women fight at Memphis strike, 6/6/37; Local 509 strikes Annshire Garment Co.; Blue Bonnet on strike with American Legion members; Betty Lou Jrs. inc. workers on strike, 4/28/54; Union members distribute a leaflet; Workers of H.W. Gossard on strike; Fifth Avenue employees strike, 8/19/52; Artificial Flower Workers' Union strikes against Supervalue Flower Co.; Sterling Neckwear employees strike, 8/6/53; Antonini, Zimmerman, Hochman standing on a platform; child of a striker holds a placard in Vanta strike, Newton, Mass., 2/1/46; men and women hold their general strike cards; women eat a meal in a room with ILGWU posters on the wall; cloak strike, 8/15/52; City Sportswear employees strike, 8/26/52; Beverly Fashions workers on strike; picketers at Page Boy talk to the operators of the shop, 1/15/53; striking women eat breakfast together
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 2 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 3 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 4 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 5 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 6 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 6)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 7 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 8 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 8)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 9 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 10 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 11 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 11)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 12 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 13 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Strikes (see also: Bx. 50 ff 23) [folder 14 of 14] (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Cleveland - selected (Box 34, Folder 15)
  Includes: portrait of local strike leaders with Hochman; three female strikers 1911, Ida Baxt (Baxter), Rose Becker, and Florence Shalor
- Strikes - Cleveland (Box 34, Folder 16)
  Includes: women marching
- Strikes - Elsing - selected (Box 34, Folder 17)
  Includes: police watch over the picket lines
- Strikes - Elsing (Box 34, Folder 18)
  Includes: Group of women employees hold up their back pay checks, McAlister, Oklahoma; striker carrying her child; children assist their parents on the picket lines; woman warms her hands by a fire during winter picketing, Jan. 1970; police escort a picketer away from the lines; policeman talks to a group of picketers
- Strikes - Judy Bond - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 34, Folder 19)
  Includes: members picket Judy Bond blouses outside a department store, 1965; Union members picket Judy Bond`s sales office in Los Angeles, 1962; union members picket outside Macy's; men wear strike placards around their necks; woman wears shirt with strike message printed on it; union members picket Judy Bond outside Gertz store
- Strikes - Judy Bond - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 1 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Includes: workers strike Judy Bond; woman hands out ILGWU bags outside store; Local 120 women distribute leaflets, Decatur, Illinois; women distribute strike information outside the Local 295 Headquarters; Asian woman carries a strike sign; woman hands out leaflets, 1962; woman hands out leaflets, 8/14/63, Boston; a teenaged daughter of an ILGWU member hands out leaflets, St. Louis, 1962; women advertise the union label, Local 128, 11/15/65; picketers display signs against Judy Bond and for the Union Label; picketers with placards asking not to buy Judy Bond blouses; black women hand out ILGWU bags in Kansas City; union members in rabbit suits appeal to customers to boycott Judy Bond during the Easter season; picketers with placards in front of Stern's Quackenbush store in Paterson, NJ, 1965; picketers in front of Bamberger's, 1965; union members picket in front of Judy Bond showrooms in NYC, 1965; picketers distribute leaflets in Minneapolis, 1964; member of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America help the ILGWU picket a Hartford department store; union members picket Iva Manufacturing Co., which supplies Judy Bond, 1964; two ILG members dressed as Santa Claus hand out union label shopping bags, Dec. 1963; Boston union plan the distribution of union label shopping bags; members of the United Steel Workers help the distribution of anti - Judy Bond shopping bags, 1963; ILGWU members distribute leaflets in front of The Fair in Chicago; policeman talks to man distributing leaflets; ILGWU members hand out leaflets in front of Stern Brothers; picketer hands out leaflets in front of Gimbel Brothers; man hands out leaflets, Aug. 1962; teenage children of union members hand out leaflets and union label shopping bags, Aug. 1962; picketers outside Frank Roy Ltd.. in Winnipeg, Canada, 1962; a Closeup picture of the anti - Judy Bond shopping bags; a union member gets a $4,800 check from the money received by the ILGWU from Judy Bond from contract violations; members of the Machinists, the Communications Workers, and the Hospital, Hotel, Motel and Restaurant Workers unions help distribute shopping bags; ILGWU members strike at the Mode O` Day factory in Burbank, California; picketers with placards, Jan. 1966; picketers outside Macy's; picketers with placards outside May. Co.; picketers outside Connie Fashion, 1964
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 2 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 3 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 4 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 5 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 6 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 7 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 8 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Strikes - Judy Bond [folder 9 of 9] (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Strikes - Kayser - Roth - selected (Box 35, Folder 10)
  Includes: picket line supporting the Kayser - Roth workers in front of the New York Stock Exchange
- Strikes - Kayser - Roth (Box 35, Folder 11)
  Includes: David Dubinsky and Antonini lead an anti-Kayser - Roth picket line; AFL-CIO members picket in front of Bloomingdale's
- Strikes - Kellwood and Ottenheimer - selected (Box 35, Folder 12)
  Includes: women with placards around their necks; picket line outside Sears; man dressed as Santa Claus walks with two children dressed in strike banners for Kellwood strike
- Strikes - Kellwood and Ottenheimer [folder 1 of 3] (Box 35, Folder 13)
  Includes: Small girl sneaks a look into Santa's gift bag at the Kellwood Striker's Children's Christmas Party; several policemen get into their cars, Nov. 1966; strikers hand out leaflets outside Sears, Nov. 1966; picket lines outside Sears; strikers taunt man driving his car to an Ottenheimer building; black woman displays a check from Kellwood for $1633, symbol of the ILGWU in background, 1973; woman gives coffee to striking women, Dec. 1966; woman warms up her cold toes, Dec. 1966; employees of Barmon Bros. strike, Westfield, NY, Feb. 1962; employees pose in front of a Kellwood sign holding their labor agreement, Jan. 1973; man holds his check for strike time from Kellwood, 1973; woman poses with a check from Kellwood in front of an ILGWU office, 1973
- Strikes - Kellwood and Ottenheimer [folder 2 of 3] (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Strikes - Kellwood and Ottenheimer [folder 3 of 3] (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Strikes - Marlene - selected [folder 1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 16)
  Includes: Picket line of strikers against Marlene Industries; two striking men who were victims of an ink - throwing attack, June, 1965
- Strikes - Marlene - selected [folder 2 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 17)
- Strikes - Marlene [folder 1 of 5] (Box 35, Folder 18)
  Includes: Copies of images of Marlene strike; picket lines outside May Co., Nov. 1969; strikers with placards; men hand out ILGWU literature outside a Marlene plant; union organizers in Marlene meet company agents, July, 1965
- Strikes - Marlene [folder 2 of 5] (Box 35, Folder 19)
- Strikes - Marlene [folder 3 of 5] (Box 35, Folder 20)
- Strikes - Marlene [folder 4 of 5] (Box 35, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Marlene [folder 5 of 5] (Box 35, Folder 22)
- Strikes - Mode O Day - selected (Box 35, Folder 23)
  Includes: Local 502 members and some children strike against Mode O' Day outside the Alamo
- Strikes - Mode O Day [folder 1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Includes: picket line outside Mode O' Day, San Bernardino, California; picket line in Salt Lake City, Utah; man with microphone interviews strikers; picketers outside a Mode O` Day store in San Antonio; picket lines outside Mode O` Day in Burbank, California; meeting of strikers, Local 453, Ottawa, Kansas
- Strikes - Mode O Day [folder 2 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Strikes - New York, 1926 - selected (Box 36, Folder 3)
  Includes: signing of agreement by Industrial Council and Union, with I. Grossman, Louis Lustig, Henry H. Finder, Louis Hyman, Morris Sprayregen, Samuel Klein, George Jablow, Morris Hillquit, Milton R. Weinberger, William Klein, on 11/13/26
- Strikes - New York, 1926 [empty folder] (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1933 & others - selected (Box 36, Folder 5)
  Includes: ILGWU strikers take a break for a soda; picketing; group photo including David Dubinsky and Julius Hochman
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1933 & others [folder 1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 6)
  Includes: Hochman, George Meany, David Dubinsky, and Antonini, 1958; Hochman - speech, 1958; Local 345 members strike against Tower City, 1958; strike committee members of Eastern Out of Town Locals 150 and 157 vote; Luigi Antonini signs a dress contract as Mayor Robert Wagner Jr., Sen. Herbert H. Lehman, and Harry Uviller look on, 1958; David Gingold - speech, 1958; strikers line up for strike assistance, New York City, 1958; strikers hand out strike leaflets, 1958; Hochman - speech to large crowd; large crowd of people voting with their hands up
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1933 & others [folder 1 of 2] (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 - selected [folder 1 of 3] (Box 36, Folder 8)
  Includes: picketers; Local 10 members picket; Dress Shipping Clerks strike with the Dressmakers; Zimmerman stands around car with strike billboard on its roof; the Dress Shipping Clerks picket; Local 148 members strike Jerry Gilden Specialties, Inc.; Hochman, David Dubinsky, Sen. Robert F. Wagner, Uviller, Herbert Lehman, and Louis Rubin hold the contract to end the strike; a series of cars with bullhorns and billboards on top of their cars; Hochman and David Dubinsky wave to a large crowd, Scranton, PA; Zimmerman with strikers with placards; Dress Shipping Clerks with placards; women in meeting with strike placards; strikers with leaflets proclaiming general strike; Scranton District strikers at Old Forge Strike Rally, 3/5/58, Old Forge, Pennsylvania
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 - selected [folder 2 of 3] (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 - selected [folder 3 of 3] (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 1 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 11)
  Includes: Meany, Hochman, and David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky, Hochman, Antonini, and Zimmerman; David Dubinsky - speech; picketers with placards; man shows his money at a strike benefit; man with his placard; woman with her placard; crowd scene at strike convention; woman sits on car with bullhorns and strike billboards; David Dubinsky and Hochman; David Dubinsky, Louis Rubin, and Hochman; workers of Cullman Lingerie, a division of Kayser - Roth, on strike in New York City; picketing in front of Marty Walker in New York City; Louis Rubin heads the delegation of Dress Manufacturers at a contract renewal hearing, 12/3/57; Hochman speaks to a group of workers in Scranton, Pennsylvania; Hochman talks to a group of employees, 12/3/57; mass of workers heads toward Madison Square Garden for a strike Meeting, 3/5/58; David Dubinsky wipes sweat off of his forehead; workers pour out of their shops after the strike call; strikers get new soles on their shoes; strikers drink coffee together; woman striker drives an Army jeep; large crowd votes with their hands up; David Dubinsky speaks to strikers; man interviews Rubin, David Dubinsky, and Hochman; Harry Uviller and Herbert H. Lehman; Harry Uviller talks to a group including Hochman; Mayor Wagner puts his arms around David Dubinsky and Rubin; group including Hochman, David Dubinsky, Lehman, Uviller, Zimmerman, Rubin, and Antonini; group including Rubin, Lehman, Uviller, David Dubinsky, and Hochman; police hold back crowds; strikers crowd into the entrance of Madison Square Garden for a strike rally; Louis Rubin talks to a group of men; David Dubinsky talks to a policeman; both parties sign agreement ending the strike, with Mayor Wagner, Rubin, Lehman, and Uviller present; Edward Kramer - speech; Saby Nehama - speech; Local 151 members in New Haven, Connecticut strike; David Dubinsky talks to Nat Boriskin of the employers; mass meeting on first day of strike in Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania; women with leaflets declaring a general strike, Rutland, Vermont; strikers take a coffee break in Allentown, Pennsylvania, 3/5/58; Local 145 members in Passaic New Jersey strike and recruit more members; Antonini leads picket line; empty dress factory, 3/6/58; picketing continues by Pennsylvania Local 60 after general strike is over, Sept. 1958; David Dubinsky holds copy of Justice; signing the Agreement; parties try to reach a last minute agreement, 2/28/58, Julius Hochman, Harry Uviller, Louis Rubin, and David Dubinsky; David Dubinsky, Herbert Lehman, Harry Uviller, and Louis Rubin shake hands, 3/11/58; David Dubinsky speaks to strikers after reaching an agreement, 3/11/58; Lehman, David Dubinsky, Isadore Agree, Louis Rubin, Harry Uviller, and Mayor Robert Wagner hold recently signed agreement, 3/13/58
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 2 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 3 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 4 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 5 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 6 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 7 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 17)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 8 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 18)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 9 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 19)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 10 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Strikes - New York Dressmakers, 1958 [folder 11 of 11] (Box 36, Folder 21)
- Strikes - Pennsylvania - selected (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Includes: David Dubinsky with a group of women strikers from Penna Dress Makers; Local 111 members picket, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1964; Pennsylvania strikers take part in the general strike, April 1958; Local 295 members march in Cleveland, 1937, with Rose Pesotta; Allentown male workers picket, 1964; Local 111 members strike against Lesavoy Mills, Allentown, 1977
- Strikes - Pennsylvania (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Includes: David Dubinsky and Antonini lead a picket line in front of Kayser - Roth; woman with placard, Lancaster, Pennsylvania; employees of Scranton Frocks Shop strike, Scranton, 1958; Local 111 members picket, 1964; union members hand out anti-Judy Bond shopping bags outside the Bon Ton, York, Pennsylvania, 1964; Locals 424-445 picket, 1980
- Strikes - Serbin - selected (Box 37, Folder 3)
  Includes: Serbin employees picket on Alabama - Tennessee state line; jubilant union members; picketers ride horses; strikers pose with their families, Fayetteville, Tennessee, 5/11/55; strikers receive a check; women in prisoner's uniforms at a strike meeting
- Strikes - Serbin [folder 1 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Includes: women pose in prisoner's uniforms; Zimmerman at a strike meeting; strikers dress in prisoner's uniforms walk with a ball and chain; Serbin strikers picket in front of Morrison Hotel, Chicago, 1955; ILGWU defendants in Lincoln County Jail; policemen; police with handcuffed striker
- Strikes - Serbin [folder 2 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Strikes - Serbin [folder 3 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Strikes - Serbin [folder 4 of 4] (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Strikes - Sears - selected (Box 37, Folder 8)
  Includes: Men, one dressed as Santa Claus, picket Sears, Dec. 1966; employees strike Sears, 1967; Local 148-162 strikes in front of Sears
- Strikes - Sears (Box 37, Folder 9)
  Includes: Police talk to black woman staging sit-in in Sears, Newark, New Jersey, 1966; police drag woman away from sit - in; man loads into police wagon; women strike in back of Sears, Paducah, Kentucky, 3/30/67; Local 346 members picket Sears, 11/6/66, Chattanooga, Tennessee; strikers picket Sears
- Strikes - Teachers, New York City - selected (Box 37, Folder 10)
  Includes: David Dubinsky, Robert Kennedy, and Stulberg; David Dubinsky, Wagner, and Potofsky; Stulberg, Sammy Davis Jr., Humphry, and Wagner
- Strikes - Teachers, New York City (Box 37, Folder 11)